An innocent crush turned deadly
My Teacher, My Obsession is a drama, thriller, tv
movie film directed by Damián Romay.
Riley is struggling to make friends after transferring to a new high
school where her father, Chris, is an English teacher.
When she meets Kyla, they quickly becomes close friends.
However, the friendship takes a strange turn when Riley
learns that Kyla is obsessed with her dad.
Will Kyla successfully seduce Chris and start a twisted new life with him by removing everyone in her path,
or will Riley be able to save her father from Kyla’s treacherous plot before it’s too late?
Chris, played by Rusty Joiner.
Kyla, played by Lucy Loken.
Riley, played by Laura Bilgeri.
Jess, played by Jana Lee Hamblin.
Tricia, played by Alexandria DeBerry.
Quentin, played by Bruno Rose.
My Teacher, My Obsession (also known as Dad Crush) is a 2018 American thriller drama film directed by Damian
Romay, written by Patrick Robert Young and starring Rusty Joiner, Lucy Loken and Laura Bilgeri.
The plot revolves around Riley (Bilgeri), who has transferred to a new high school
where her father Chris (Joiner) is working as an English teacher.
Riley initially has a hard time finding new friends, but eventually
meets Kyla (Loken) and they become close friends.
It turns out, though, that Kyla is obsessed with Riley's father.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.